in this video we're going to think about
在这个视频中，我们将考虑
how to bid in a second price auction
如何竞标第二次价格
remember that a second price auction is
请记住，第二次价格拍卖是
one in which a single good is being sold
出售一种商品的商品
all of the bidders submit their bids in
所有投标人都在
sealed envelopes the auctioneer looks at
拍卖师看的密封信封
all of the bids Awards the good to the
所有的标书都对
person who bid highest and makes them
出价最高并达到最高的人
pay the second highest amount and what
支付第二高的金额以及什么
we want to think about here is how you
我们想在这里想你
should actually bid what makes sense to
实际上应该出价对
do in a second-price auction the main
在第二价格拍卖中
claim of this lecture today is that
今天这堂课的主张是
truth-telling is a dominant strategy in
讲真话是占主导地位的策略
a second price auction so in other words
换句话说，就是第二次拍卖
no matter how the other bidders are
不管其他竞标者如何
going to behave the right thing for you
会为你做正确的事
to do in a second price auction is to
在第二次价格拍卖中要做的是
bid the amount that the good is actually
出价商品的实际价值
worth to you now in fact you should know
现在对您有价值，实际上您应该知道
this already and the reason is that a
这已经是，原因是
second price auction is a special case
二次拍卖是特例
of the VCG mechanism remember that in
的VCG机制请记住
VCG every bidder is paid the amount of
每位竞标者获得的VCG金额为
utility that all of the other bidders
所有其他竞标者的效用
get in the world where they exist and
进入他们存在的世界，
then is charged the amount of utility
然后要收取水电费
that all of the other bidders get in the
所有其他竞标者都参与了
world where they don't exist in the case
在这种情况下不存在的世界
of a second price auction where there's
在第二次价格拍卖中
only one good no other bidders get any
只有一种商品没有其他竞标者
utility in the case where I win and one
我赢了一个的情况下的效用
other bidder gets utility in the case
其他投标人在这种情况下获得效用
where I lose that's the person who would
我失去的是那个会
have won if I hadn't participated so I
如果我没有参加的话就赢了，所以我
should be paid zero and I should have to
应该被支付零，我应该
pay the second highest price and that's
支付第二高的价格，那就是
exactly what the second price auction
究竟是第二次价格拍卖
does so in a sense that's all you need
从某种意义上讲，这就是您所需要的
to know from this lecture but I'd like
从这次演讲中知道，但是我想
to show you a simpler more direct proof
向您展示更简单直接的证明
that doesn't rely on VCG because the the
这不依赖VCG，因为
VCG
truthfulness proof is a bit abstract
真实性证明有点抽象
here I can give a very intuitive proof
在这里我可以给出一个非常直观的证明
that that I think it's an elegant way of
我认为这是一种优雅的方式
seeing why truthfulness is the right
明白为什么诚实是正确的
thing to do at a second price auction so
要做第二次拍卖的事情
the proof is going to work as follows
证明将如下工作
we're going to assume that the other
我们将假设另一个
bidders bid arbitrarily that's important
投标人任意投标很重要
because we want to show that it's a
因为我们想证明它是一个
dominant strategy to bid truthfully so I
诚实出价的主导策略，所以我
can't make any assumption how
不能做任何假设
the other bidders will behave and I want
其他竞标者会表现得很好，我想要
to show that no matter what the right
表示无论什么权利
thing for a bidder I to do is to respond
我要投标人要做的是回应
by bidding truthfully and I'm going to
通过如实竞标，我将
consider two cases the case where if
考虑两种情况
bidder I bid honestly he would win the
投标人我诚实地说，他会赢得
auction and the case where if bidding
拍卖和竞价的情况
honestly he would lose the auction so
老实说他会输掉拍卖，所以
let's start by thinking about the case
让我们先考虑一下情况
where bidding honestly bitter eye wins
说实话，苦涩的眼睛胜出
the auction in this case we can sort of
在这种情况下的拍卖，我们可以
look at this picture here so here we
在这里看这张照片所以在这里我们
have eyes true value at this level here
在此水平上具有眼睛的真实价值
and and then here we have the amount
然后我们有数量
that I bid now we're saying that I bids
我现在出价我是说我出价
truthfully I initially and so that means
老实说我一开始就是这样
that his bid is at this amount here and
他的出价是这个价位，
of course in a second-price auction the
当然，在第二价拍卖中
amount that I actually pays is not his
我实际支付的金额不是他的
bid but it's the amount of the second
出价，但这是第二个的金额
highest price which we'd shown here all
我们在这里显示的最高价格
right so let's let's do a kind of case
好的，让我们来做一个案例
analysis and think about what would have
分析并考虑会发生什么
happened if I had been differently if I
如果我与众不同，就会发生
were to bid higher then he would still
出价更高，那么他仍然会
win and he would still pay the same
赢了，他仍然会付出相同的代价
amount so nothing would change if he
金额，所以如果他
were to bid lower just a bit lower
叫低一点
again nothing would change as long as
只要什么都不会改变
he's still higher than the next highest
他仍然比第二高
bidder but if he bid sufficiently lower
投标人，但如果他的投标价足够低
then he would stop being the highest
然后他将不再是最高
bidder and he would lose the auction and
投标人，他将输掉拍卖，
instead the next highest bidder would
相反，第二高的出价者会
win so what we can see here is that in
赢了，所以我们在这里可以看到的是
the case where I has the highest
我最高的情况
valuation and he changes his bid four
估价，他更改了出价四
things can happen three of them it
事情可能会发生三个
doesn't make any difference to him and
对他没有任何影响
in one case something changes and what's
在一种情况下，某些事情发生了变化，这是什么
important here is in the case where
重要的是
something changes things get worse for
事情改变了，事情变得更糟
bidder I because he used to be getting
投标人我，因为他曾经
positive utility right there was this
积极的效用就在那里
utility difference here between how much
这里的效用差多少
he valued the good how much utility he
他珍惜好多少
gets for consuming the good and how much
消费商品以及获取多少
he has to pay so he was getting positive
他必须付款，所以他变得积极起来
utility here and he
实用在这里，他
when he loses he's getting zero utility
当他输了时，他的效用为零
because he doesn't get the good and
因为他没有得到好处
bitter I would prefer to be in this
苦我宁愿在这个
situation with positive utility than
效用大于
this situation with zero utility and so
效用为零的情况等等
it's the wrong thing for him in the case
这件事对他来说是错的
where he has the highest valuation to
他的估值最高
bid any way other than truthfully what
除了真实地出价以外，还可以出价
about the case where he wouldn't be the
关于他不会成为的情况
winner if he were to bid honestly well
如果他要诚实地出价，那就是赢家
in this case if he bids lower he would
在这种情况下，如果他降低出价，他会
still lose and pay nothing if he bids a
如果他竞标
bit higher he'll again still lose and
再高一点，他仍然会输
pay nothing and if he bids high enough
不付钱，如果他出价足够高
he'll eventually win but in this case if
他最终会赢，但在这种情况下，
he wins he's going to pay this amount
他赢了，他要付这笔钱
which we know is higher than his
我们知道比他高
valuation and so he by bidding
估价，所以他通过竞标
untruthfully in the case where he isn't
如果他不在，那是不诚实的
the highest bidder he's either going to
他要去的最高出价者
pay too much pay more than the good is
付出太多而不是付出更多
worth to him or he's going to not affect
对他来说值得，否则他不会影响
the outcome and so again we can see that
结果，所以我们可以再次看到
there's no way that bidder I can gain by
我无法通过任何方式获得竞标者
changing his bid and and that's the
改变他的出价，那就是
whole proof notice that we didn't have
整个证明，我们没有
to assume anything about the
承担有关
relationship between other people's bids
他人出价之间的关系
and their own valuations and because of
和他们自己的估值，并且由于
that we've shown that it's a dominant
我们已经证明它是主导
strategy for bidder I to disclose
投标人我披露的策略
truthfully to the auctioneer what his
真实地告诉拍卖师他的
valuation is now I'd like to end by just
估值现在我只想结束
making a remark about English and
发表关于英语和
Japanese auctions these are much more
日本拍卖会更多
complicated auctions in that they define
他们定义了复杂的拍卖
extensive forum games rather than normal
广泛的论坛游戏，而不是正常的
forum games so bidders are able to
论坛游戏，使投标者能够
observe something about how other
观察其他事情
bidders have behaved in the auction they
竞标者在拍卖中表现得很好
can condition their bids on this
可以对此出价
information in the case of English
关于英文的信息
auctions bidders have a rich set of
拍卖竞标者有丰富的
strategic options at every stage they
他们在每个阶段的战略选择
can decide not just whether to drop out
不仅可以决定是否辍学
or stay in but they can decide to place
或留下来，但他们可以决定放置
what's called a jump in to to make a
所谓的跳进去做一个
unit to bid from kind of two dollars to
单位竞标价格从两美元到
go all the way to ten dollars but
一路走到十美元，但
intuitively in the case of independent
在独立的情况下直观地
private values this revealed information
私人珍视此信息
doesn't make any difference so we can
没有任何区别，所以我们可以
show that in the independent private
表明在独立私人
values model it's a dominant strategy
价值观模型是一种主导策略
for bidders to bid up to and not beyond
投标人可以出价至不超过
their valuation
他们的估值
in both Japanese and English junctions
在日语和英语交汇处
and so in a sense Japanese English and
从某种意义上讲，日语，英语和
second price auctions are all kind of
第二价格拍卖都是
the same in the case of independent
独立的情况相同
private values
私人价值观